Guide to the James G. Harbord Papers 1902-1949 MS 1493
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: General correspondence
  - Subseries I.1: Correspondence A-Z
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Belleau Wood Memorial Association", 1923-August 1924 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", June 1933-1937 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", May 1933 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", December 1932-April 1933 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", April-November 1932 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", May 1931-March 1932 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", January-March 1931 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", November-December 1930 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", July-October 1930 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", January-June 1930 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", 1929 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", 1928 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", 1927 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", 1925-1926 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", 1924 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", January 1924 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", October-December 1923 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bok Peace Award, American Foundation", September 1923 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Budget: Military, Appropriations and Bonus", 1931-1933 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 1)
      Harbord belonged to the National Committee against the Prepayment of the Bonus, which opposed the early payout (1932) of the 1924 veteran bonus of $1000 (redeemable in 1945); he supported Hoover's veto of Bonus Bill and opposed the Bonus Marchers/Army
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bush Terminal Suit", 1942-1944 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 2)
      Harbord was involved in a suit against the Bush Terminal Co. in his capacity as financial investor and manager
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bush Terminal Suit", 1941 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bush Terminal Suit", September-December 1940 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bush Terminal Suit (Copies of Appeals and Testimony)", 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bush Terminal Suit (Letters from Frank Bailey)", 1936-August 1940 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Bush Terminal Suit", 1918-1933 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Chamber of Commerce of United States", November 1925-1926 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Chamber of Commerce of United States", May-September 1925 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Chamber of Commerce of United States (Committee for American Merchant Marine)", 1924-1925 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-China Society of America", 1931-1932 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-China Society of America", 1924-1930 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Citizens Reconstruction Organization", 1932 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Colprovia Roads, Inc.", 1948 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Conseil International De Reserches, International Auxiliary Language Association of the United States", 1934-1945 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Conseil International De Reserches, International Auxiliary Language Association of the United States", 1926-1933 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Conseil International De Reserches, International Auxiliary Language Association of the United States", 1923-1925 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Durant Prize Committee", 1928-1929 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Federal International Banking Co.", 1931-1932 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Federal International Banking Co.", January-Mid-April 1931 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Federal International Banking Co.", December 1930 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Federal International Banking Co.", January-October 1930 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Federal International Banking Co. (Prospectus)", 1929 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Federal International Banking Co.", 1928-1929 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Grant Monument Association", 1938-1946 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Grant Monument Association", 1929-1937 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Industrial Rehabilitation", 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", September 1930-1939 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 6)
      photographs; oversized document (leprosy fund ad)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", March-August 1930 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", August 1929-January 1930 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", March-July 1929 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", October 1928-February 1929 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", June-September 1928 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", April-May 1928 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", February-March 1928 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", December 1927-January 1928 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", October-November 1927 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", August-September 1927 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", March-June 1927 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Leprosy Eradication Fund", 1923-1925 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Military Order of the World War", 1937-1947 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Military Order of the World War", 1931-1936 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Military Order of the World War", 1927-April 1931 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Military Order of the World War", 1926 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 22)
      Neuby Memorandum scandal (allegations of "socialism, communism, outlawry of war, and sex irregularity")
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Military Order of the World War", November-December 1925 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Military Order of the World War", March-October 1925 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Military Order of the World War", November 1924-February 1925 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 1)
      Includes pamphlets and correspondence about allegations against Federal Council of Churches of communism, socialism, and pacifism (considered anti-patriotism).
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Military Order of the World War", March 1923-October 1924 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Military Training Camp Association", 1923-1934 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Moro Educational Foundation", 1935-1940 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Moro Educational Foundation", May 1932-December 1933 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Moro Educational Foundation", July 1929-March 1932 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Moro Educational Foundation", January-June 1929 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Moro Educational Foundation", January 1925-September 1928 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Moro Educational Foundation", January 1923-January 1925 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Civic Federation", 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Civic Federation", 1928-1937 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Civic Federation", 1923-1927 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Emergency Committee, Military Training Camps Association", October 1940-1941 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Emergency Committee, Military Training Camps Association", July-September 1940 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 15)
      There is correspondence from Theodore Roosevelt in several "National Republican Club" folders.
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", 1940-1943 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", 1939 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", April 1936-1938 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", 1935-March 1936 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", 1934 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", March-December 1933 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", June 1932-February 1933 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", March-May 1932 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", January-February 1932 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", August-December 1931 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", Mid-June-July 1931 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club", March-June 1931 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Republican Club (Saturday Discussions)", 1931-1932 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Security League", May 1924-1933 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-National Security League", 1923-April 1924 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Near East Relief", 1930-1937 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 8)
      New Year's photo booklet of orphans "rescued" by "American ideals"
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Near East Relief", October 1924-1925 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Near East Relief", February-September 1924 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Near East Relief", February 1923-January 1924 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Near East Relief", August 1928-1929 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Near East Relief", August 1927-January 1928 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Near East Relief", October 1926-June 1927 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Near East Relief", December 1925-September 1926 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Near East Relief", March-November 1925 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-New York Good Will Election (American Good Will Association)", 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-New York Good Will Election (American Good Will Association)", September-December 1926 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-New York Good Will Election (American Good Will Association)", May 1925-August 1926 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-New York Good Will Election (American Good Will Association)", May 1924-March 1925 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-New York Good Will Election (American Good Will Association)", May 1923-1924 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-New York Good Will Election (American Good Will Association)", January-April 1923 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-New York Ordinance District", 1926-1933 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-New York Ordinance District", 1924-1926 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Photomaton Incorporated", 1927-1930 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 3)
      Harbord was not actually a board member; correspondence was in response to a misprinting
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Philippine Society", 1941-1947 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Philippine Society", 1934-1940 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Philippine Society", 1928-1932 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Philippine Society", May 1925-1927 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Philippine Society", 1923-January 1925 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Princeton University", 1933-1936 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Republican Campaign for Mayor", 1929-1933 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Republican Campaign for Mayor", 1929 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Republican Campaigns", November 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Republican Campaigns", October 1932 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 13)
      Includes seating charts/maps of Madison Square Garden in 1933
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Republican County Committee (Salmon Tower)", 1931-1934 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 14)
      blue prints and lease for tower
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Republican County Committee (Salmon Tower Lawsuit)", 1931-1932 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Republican County Committee", 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 16)
      letters from (and signed by) Herbert Hoover across "Republican County Committee" folders
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Republican County Committee", October 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Republican County Committee", January-September 1930 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Santo Domingo (Dawes Commission)", May 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Santo Domingo (Dawes Commission)", March-May 1929 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Santo Domingo (Dawes Commission)", 1928-February 1929 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Santo Domingo (Dawes Commission)", 1928 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", 1935-1937 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", May-November 1934 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", January-March 1934 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", November 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", June 1931-August 1932 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", July 1930-May 1931 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", January-June 1930 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", July-December 1929 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", February-June 1929 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", November 1925-January 1928 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Association", April 1923-October 1925 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund Contributions (List of Amounts and Contributors)", 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund Contributions (List of Amounts and Contributors)", 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund Contributions (Officers)", 1930-1936 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund Contributions", October 1935-October 1936 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund Contributions", September 1935 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund Contributions", August 1935 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund Contributions", July 1935 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund Contributions", 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund Contributions (Government Funding)", 1930-1934 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", 1936 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 20)
      Note for all "Memberships-Etc." folders: the "Memberships-Etc." category is spread across boxes 29, 30, and 33, reflecting the original order.
      Most correspondence is soliciting Harbord's donation or name as founder/member (to which he mostly declines). Frequent and notable correspondents include Colonel Edward Olmstead; Major Muller; Trinity College; Major General M.W. Ireland.
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", December 1935 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 21)
      Includes Louise Alice Williams "Cabin Stories and Plantation Songs" (Southern Belle performances)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", November 16-30, 1935 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 22)
      Includes American Social Hygiene Association (pamphlet on sex education); material on The Adventure Society.
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", November 1-15, 1935 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 23)
      American Social Hygiene Association (pamphlet on sex education); The Adventure Society
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", October 17-31, 1935 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", October 1-15, 1935 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", September 12-30, 1935 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", September 1-11, 1935 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", Mid-July-August 1935 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Etc.", June-Mid-July 1935 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 5)
      Includes Ancient and Noble Order of the Blue Lamoo (Aryan Brotherhood).
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", 1943-1947 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 6)
      Second Division Memorial Fund was originally 4 separate sections: Second Division Memorial Fund, Second Division Memorial Fund (Originals sent to Miss Mulkins), Second Division for Miss Kay, Replies to Contributions to Second Division Memorial Fund. Includes documents pertaining to funding and building of monument; photos of memorial; design plans; donation records and solicitation.
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", 1940-1942 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", 1937-1939 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", August-December 1936 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", July 1936 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", Mid-October 1935-June 1936 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", Beginning-Mid-October 1935 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", July-September 1935 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", June 1935 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", January-May 1935 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", October-December 1934 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", August-September 1934 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", 1932-July 1934 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", 1931 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", July-December 1930 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", January-June 1930 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Second Division Memorial Fund", 1926-1929 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Sentinels of the Republic (Endowment Fund)", 1929 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Sentinels of the Republic (Endowment Fund)", 1928 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Sentinels of the Republic (Endowment Fund)", July 1926-1927 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Sentinels of the Republic (Endowment Fund)", April-June 1926 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Sentinels of the Republic (Endowment Fund)", 1929-1935 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Sentinels of the Republic", June 1935-1939 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Sentinels of the Republic", 1932-May 1935 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Sentinels of the Republic", 1932-1933 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Sentinels of the Republic", 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Sentinels of the Republic", 1926-1929 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Unemployment Relief", March-September 1933 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Unemployment Relief", December 1932-February 1933 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Unemployment Relief", April-November 1932 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence "Memberships-Unemployment Relief", December 1931-March 1932 (Offsite-box 31, Folder 17)